[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many directions does the compass have?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "1", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturn is the Roman name of which Greek deity?", "correct_answer": "Kronos", "incorrect_answers": ["Styx", "Ourobouros", "Pan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rastafarianism is a religion that venerates Haile Selassie as a god. Haile Selassie was the emperor of the third most populous country in Africa. Name that country.", "correct_answer": "Ethiopia", "incorrect_answers": ["Libya", "Mozambique", "Gabon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1955, when trying to convince his teenage father George McFly to ask Lorraine out, Marty appears in a radiation suit and says his name is what?", "correct_answer": "Darth Vader", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Spock", "Captain Kirk", "Luke Skywalker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cavities are generally painless. However, if not treated, they enlarge and eventually become painful as they reach the internal structure of the tooth, especially this part.", "correct_answer": "Dentin", "incorrect_answers": ["Enamel", "Calculus", "Root"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish these lyrics from the song Karazy performed by Jackass star Chris Pontius:\nYou think you know Karate, well I know Karazy, Im always Rockin and Rollin except when __________.", "correct_answer": "Im feelin lazy", "incorrect_answers": ["Im feelin Phrasy", "Im smelling daisies", "I am feeling Hazy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For the 1954 rendition of A Star is Born, both James Mason and Judy Garland were nominated for Oscars in the tops spots \u2013 Best Actor in a Leading Role and Best Actress in a Leading Role.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the national anthem of the Italian Republic?", "correct_answer": "The Song of the Italians", "incorrect_answers": ["The Italian Anthem", "Italia, Land of Glory", "Italian Dream"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Chris Gardners son in the drama film The Pursuit of Happyness?", "correct_answer": "Jaden Christopher Syre Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobby Pinkett", "Bobby Smith", "Jared Pinkett"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the other name for the Achilles tendon, which acts as a connection between the calf and the heel in humans?", "correct_answer": "Calcaneal tendon", "incorrect_answers": ["Glenohumeral joint", "Teres major", "Chordae tendinae"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the listed words links a World War II destroyer, the band Teenage Fanclub and a murderous clown called Pennywise?", "correct_answer": "King", "incorrect_answers": ["Kendo", "Kettle", "Kiki"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would have a college education?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "14", "20"]}]